Alright, the job finished.
It took about 11 minutes only this time
because we used five workers.
So what's the next step? Now, next step,
if you remember from the previous steps we did
for the curated layer, even for the aggregated layer,
we gotta do a unit testing before we hand over the
data to data analyst, right?
So we are gonna go to the log
and click on third put logs
that's gonna open the CloudWatch log.
We'll scroll down finally and then take a look at this.
Okay. Uh, it shows that, uh, the original curated record for
so many, which is the right number
that we saw in Curated as well.
It has created three tables
and we have the number of records in these tables as well.
But again, we've gotta go
and really query in Athena to really validate this.
And we've gotta also be unit testing whether the aggregation
has been done properly or not,
before we hand over the data to the data.
So let's do that in this video. So what's the first step?
First step is to create the crawler.